var quiz = [{"answers": ["newspapers", "desertification", "advertisements", "graphs"], "correctIndex": 1, "question": "All of the following are examples of signifying practices, EXCEPT:"}, {"answers": ["True", "False"], "correctIndex": 1, "question": "The most important part of constructivism is proving that a concept is false."}, {"answers": ["True", "False"], "correctIndex": 0, "question": "The social relations that generated the concept of race are very real, but there is no scientific basis to prove the existence of different races of people."}, {"answers": ["material realities", "discourses", "signifying practices", "relativism"], "correctIndex": 1, "question": "The pristine myth of the New World and North African desertification are examples of _______ that benefited Europeans in their colonial expansion."}, {"answers": ["True", "False"], "correctIndex": 1, "question": "Human perceptions about nature have varied very little over time."}, {"answers": ["True", "False"], "correctIndex": 1, "question": "The theory of co-production argues that all beliefs, truths, and facts are socially constructed in a particular social context."}, {"answers": ["None of the choices is correct", "Science is an objective method for discovering the truth of nature", "All beliefs, truths, and facts are constructed in a particular social context", "Natural laws determine the way humans relate to one another"], "correctIndex": 2, "question": "A relativist would most likely argue that _______."}, {"answers": ["concept", "ideology", "narrative", "context"], "correctIndex": 3, "question": "A discourse includes all of the following, EXCEPT:"}, {"answers": ["What are the social effects of believing this concept is inevitable?", "All of these questions can be asked.", "Under what conditions was this concept invented?", "Is the concept universal?"], "correctIndex": 1, "question": "Which of the following questions could we ask ourselves to determine if something is socially constructed?"}, {"answers": ["Whether science is socially constructed.", "What are the topics that interest the scientific community.", "What counts as \u201cgood\u201d science.", "Who funds the science."], "correctIndex": 0, "question": "Social constructivists question all of the following regarding science in constructivism, EXCEPT:"}, {"answers": ["social construct", "narrative", "discourse", "ideology"], "correctIndex": 1, "question": "A story with a beginning and an end is called a(n):"}, {"answers": ["discourse", "natural law", "ideology", "signifying practices"], "correctIndex": 0, "question": "The concept of power/knowledge is used to remind us there are relations of power embedded in all knowledge and what?"}, {"answers": ["Social context", "Relativism", "Social construction", "Discourse"], "correctIndex": 2, "question": "The theory that any category, condition, or thing is understood to have certain characteristics because people agree that it does is called:"}, {"answers": ["power/knowledge", "relativism", "co-production", "constructivism"], "correctIndex": 2, "question": "The theory of _______ argues that humans and non-humans produce and change one another through interactions with each other."}, {"answers": ["True", "False"], "correctIndex": 0, "question": "A social constructivist examines how beliefs, values, and practices shape how people understand the world."}, {"answers": ["True", "False"], "correctIndex": 1, "question": "Discourse is spoken and written language and therefore cannot alter the material world."}, {"answers": ["True", "False"], "correctIndex": 1, "question": "Before the \u201cNew World\u201d was discovered by Christopher Columbus, the land was pristine and undeveloped."}, {"answers": ["Power/knowledge", "Narrative", "Relativism", "Discourse"], "correctIndex": 0, "question": "_______ is a concept that is used to explore how knowledge is created and sustained in a field of social relations of power."}, {"answers": ["constructivism", "relativism", "co-production", "discourse"], "correctIndex": 1, "question": "The problem with __________ is that there are things and systems that operate independently of human behavior, no matter what knowledge we construct of them."}, {"answers": ["Determine the origins of discourse that have influenced environmental knowledge.", "Enforce existing environmental discourses as a mode of power.", "Destabilize environmental discourses.", "Uncover the institutions that sustain the discourses."], "correctIndex": 1, "question": "Social constructionists attempt to do all of the following, EXCEPT:"}, {"answers": ["True", "False"], "correctIndex": 0, "question": "In the concept of power/knowledge, marginalized entities can use power to challenge dominant discourses."}, {"answers": ["True", "False"], "correctIndex": 0, "question": "Nature is socially constructed."}, {"answers": ["relativism", "discourse", "constructivism", "co-production"], "correctIndex": 0, "question": "The theory that all beliefs, truths, and facts are socially constructed in a particular social context is called:"}, {"answers": ["It places focus on places assumed to be wilderness.", "The concept of wilderness is constantly shifting.", "Focuses on valuable natural areas or conditions.", "Wilderness has been inhabited and altered by people."], "correctIndex": 2, "question": "Which of the following is NOT true regarding wilderness discourse?"}, {"answers": ["True", "False"], "correctIndex": 0, "question": "Michel Foucault\u2019s point is the goals of power and the goals of knowledge cannot be separated: in knowing we control and in controlling we know."}, {"answers": ["discourse", "ideology", "narrative", "concept"], "correctIndex": 1, "question": "A(n) _______ is a belief about how the world is and how it ought to be."}, {"answers": ["ideology", "social context", "narrative", "discourse"], "correctIndex": 3, "question": "The term that describes spoken and written language that not only represents the world, but may materially change it, is called:"}, {"answers": ["The material world itself", "Nature is society", "Essential quality of something", "Inherent force that directs humans"], "correctIndex": 1, "question": "Which of the following is NOT a meaning for \u201cnature\u201d?"}, {"answers": ["they wanted to justify colonial expansion into the territory.", "they found the land barren and in need of intervention.", "Native Americans had not altered their environment.", "it was uninhabited when they discovered it."], "correctIndex": 0, "question": "Europeans described the New World as pristine because:"}, {"answers": ["constructivism", "co-production", "discourse", "power/knowledge"], "correctIndex": 1, "question": "An alternative concept to relativism is:"}]

quizCollection['8'] = quiz
